Inventory of the James Robert Huntley papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Individuals countries and regions
  - Islamic world, Middle East, 1985-1992 (Box-folder 313: 7)
  - Turkey, 1974-1997 (Box-folder 313: 8)
  - Iran, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 313: 9)
- Atlantic-Pacific relations (West), 1975-1993 (Box-folder 314: 1)
- Individuals countries and regions
  - USA, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 314: 2)
  - Washington State's international ties, 1980-1992 (Box-folder 314: 3)
  - Seattle, 1974-2001 (Box-folder 314: 4)
  - North America, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 314: 5)
  - Alaska, 1997 (Box-folder 314: 6)
  - California, 1989 (Box-folder 314: 7)
  - General, 1985-2003 (Box-folder 314: 8)
  - Brazil, 1975-1989 (Box-folder 314: 9)
- Atlantic-Pacific relations (West)
  - Indian Ocean defense, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 315: 1)
  - Bibliographies, 1973-1988 (Box-folder 315: 2)
  - Political, 1976-1995 (Box-folder 315: 3)
  - General, 1976-1999 (Box-folder 315: 4-5)
  - Economic Union, 1990 (Box-folder 315: 6)
  - Association of South East Asian Nations (ASEAN), 1984-1996 (Box-folder 315: 7)
  - Pacific Caucus, 1985 (Box-folder 315: 8)
  - Asia/Pacific Economic Cooperative Group, 1990-1995 (Box-folder 315: 9)
- Biographical file
  - Huntley biography, 1960-1979 (Box-folder 316: 1)
  - Career plans, 1972-1999 (Box-folder 316: 2)
- Atlantic-Pacific relations (West)
  - Economic, 1978-1997 (Box-folder 316: 3)
  - Strategic and defense, 1978-1995 (Box-folder 316: 4)
  - Japan, Canada, Australian, New Zealand United States(JACANANZUS), Rim of the Pacific Exercise (RIMPAC), 1979-1990 (Box-folder 316: 5)
- Biographies
  - A-C, 1979-1996 (Box-folder 317: 1)
  - D-F, 1980-2002 (Box-folder 317: 2)
  - G-I, 1979-2004 (Box-folder 317: 3)
  - J-L, 1981-2002 (Box-folder 317: 4)
  - M-O, 1981-1999 (Box-folder 317: 5)
  - P-R, 1982-2004 (Box-folder 317: 6)
  - S-U, 1977-2003 (Box-folder 317: 7)
  - V-X, 1982-2000 (Box-folder 317: 8)
- Association to Unite the Democracies, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 317: 9)
- Arthur G. Barnett, attorney for plaintiffs, 1988 (Box-folder 317: 10)
  Includes pleadings of case for which Huntley was a plaintiff.
- Correspondence, biography, 1977-2002 (Box-folder 317: 11)
- Association to Unite the Democracies, Next Century Initiative, G. Russel, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 318: 1)
- Council for a Community of Democracies (Next Century Initiative)
  - Soros, 1997-2001 (Box-folder 318: 2)
  - Foundations, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 318: 3)
  - Jackson School of International Studies (JSIS), 2002 (Box-folder 318: 4)
  - Borden fundraising, 2000-2004 (Box-folder 318: 5-6)
  - Transformation, 1999 (Box-folder 319: 1)
  - Programs, 1999 (Box-folder 319: 2)
  - General, 1999-2003 (Box-folder 319: 3)
  - Legal documents, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 319: 4)
  - Santiago, 2003 (Box-folder 319: 5)
  - Administration, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 319: 6)
  - Gates, 1991-2004 (Box-folder 319: 7)
  - Pax Democratica, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 319: 8)
  - Finance, 1999-2004 (Box-folder 319: 9)
  - Fundraising, 1999-2004 (Box-folder 319: 10)
  - Small grants, 1999-2004 (Box-folder 319: 11)
  - Russel, 2000-2004 (Box-folder 319: 12)
  - Germany, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 320: 1)
  - Europe, 2001-2004 (Box-folder 320: 2)
  - Canada, 2000-2004 (Box-folder 320: 3)
  - Form of federations, 2003 (Box-folder 320: 4)
  - Australia and New Zealand, 2001 (Box-folder 320: 5)
  - Japan, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 320: 6)
  - Outside Europe and intergovernmental organizations (IGOs), 2001-2003 (Box-folder 320: 7)
  - "Albright's Democratic Plan," L.A. Times, 1999 (Box-folder 320: 8)
  - Next Century Initiative origins and correspondence, 1993-2004 (Box-folder 320: 9)
  - Purchases promotion, 1995-2004 (Box-folder 320: 10)
  - Next Century Initiative, 1994-2001 (Box-folder 320: 11)
  - General, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 320: 12)
  - 1st initial meeting, full set of conference documents, 1982 November (Box-folder 321: 1)
- Second Strasbourg Conference on Parliamentary Democracy, compendium of documents, 1987 September (Box-folder 321: 2)
- Consortium for Atlantic-Pacific Affairs (CAPA), 1977 (Box-folder 321: 3-6)
- Committees for a Community of Democracies
  - London, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 322: 1)
  - Europe, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 322: 2)
  - San Francisco, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 322: 3)
  - CCDs in LCDs, Association of Democracies, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 322: 4)
  - Book 1, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 323: 1-4)
  - All Democracies Conference, 1988 (Box-folder 323: 5-7)
  - Foreign Affairs: The Summit, 1985 (Box-folder 324: 1)
  - Foreign Affairs, 1983 (Box-folder 324: 2)
  - Book 2, 1977-1987 (Box-folder 324: 3-6)
  - International Steering Group (ISG) book, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 324: 7-8)
- Battelle Memorial Institute
  - Science Policy Reviews, 1972 (Box-folder 325: 1)
  - "How to Change the World: Better Environment,", undated (Box-folder 325: 2)
  - Human affairs centers, undated (Box-folder 325: 3)
- Bundestag Youth Exchange for Young Professionals, study materials, 1985 (Box-folder 325: 4-7)
- Bundestag Youth Exchange for Young Professionals, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 326: 1)
- "Deutsches Youth for Understanding Komitee e. V.,", 1983 December (Box-folder 326: 2)
- Foundation for Cohesion of the West, U.S. planning group and prospectus, book 1 and 2, 1986-1993 (Box-folder 326: 3-7)
- Congress-Bundestag Rotary Exchange Program, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 327: 1-7)
- Weyerhaeuser Leadership Institute, 1988 (Box-folder 327: 8-9)
- Foreign Affairs, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 328: 1-3)
- Foreign Affairs: America and the World, 1985 (Box-folder 328: 4)
- Congress-Bundestag Rotary Exchange Program, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 328: 5-8)
- Foreign Affairs, 1985-2001 (Box-folder 329: 1-8)
- International affairs, printed matter
  - "The Atlantic Council of the United States: Issues and Options,", 1988 (Box 330)
  - "The Atlantic Council of the United States: Policy Papers,", 1987 (Box 330)
  - "Inventory of International Capabilities of the University of South Carolina Faculty and Staff,", 1985-1986 (Box 330)
  - "A Foreign Policy for the United States,", 1987 May (Box 330)
  - APPU Quarterly, 1986 February (Box 330)
  - "JCIE Program Report,", 1983-1984 (Box 330)
  - Committees for a Community of Democracies, 1982 (Box 330)
  - "Managing National Security: The Reagan/Mondale Challenge,", 1984 (Box 330)
  - "A Foreign Policy for the United States,", 1987 (Box 330)
  - "MacWorld: The Key to Excel,", 1986 June (Box 330)
  - "The Future of the Western Community" Proceedings, 1985 October (Box 330)
  - Atlantic Community Newsletter, 1986 April-May (Box 330)
  - Occidente, 1984 (Box 330)
  - United States Advisory Commission on Public Diplomacy, 1986 (Box 330)
  - "The Uncertainty Principle,", 1986 (Box 330)
  - "15th Annual Report to the Congress,", 1985 (Box 330)
  - "Encounter" pamphlet, undated (Box 330)
  - "Postwar Politics: Liberalism Versus Social Democracy,", 1983 (Box 330)
  - "Deutsch-Amerikanische Gesellschaft,", 1982 (Box 330)
  - "The Alliance Papers,", undated (Box 330)
  - "Canada and Western Security,", 1982 (Box 330)
  - Twenty-First Cosmos Club Award, 1984 May (Box 330)
  - Presse Club Munchen E.V., 1980 (Box 330)
  - "Shaping Communities,", 1984 (Box 330)
  - "Terrorism in Theory and Practice,", 1978 (Box 330)
  - "The Toyota Foundation: Fiscal Year Report,", 1984 (Box 330)
- Pamphlets and reports, INSEAD and others, 1965-1983 (Box 331)
- Foreign Affairs files, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 332: 1-4)
  Includes printed copy of "A New Look at U.S. cultural and Educational Policy in Europe" by Huntley.
- Pamphlets and brochures, 1980s (Box-folder 332: 5)
- "The Ford Foundation: Annual Report,", 1950-1958 (Box-folder 333: 1-9)
- "The Ford Foundation: Annual Report,", 1960-1964 (Box-folder 334: 1-5)
- Council for a Community of Democracies (Next Century Initiative), 2001-2005 (Box-folder 334: 6)
- Contacts, alphabetical card file, undated (Boxes 335-339)
- International Relations General, 2008 (Box-folder 340: 1-2)
- Bush and Pax Americana, 2001-2008 (Box-folder 340: 3)
- Far Right, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 340: 4)
- Democracy, civic culture, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 340: 5)
- Economy, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 340: 6)
- Atlantic Community, security, 2007-2009 (Box-folder 340: 7)
- Anti-democracy axis, 2009 June-July (Box-folder 340: 8)
- Europe, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 340: 9)
- Individual countries, 2005-2009 (Box-folder 340: 10)
- Education, 2007-2009 (Box-folder 340: 11)
- Non-governmental organizations (NGOs), 2007-2009 (Box-folder 340: 12)
- Streit Council, 2009 June-July (Box-folder 341: 1)
- Hoover Institution, 2009 August (Box-folder 341: 2)
- Foundations and philanthropy, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 341: 3)
- Uniting the Democracies, 1979 (Box-folder 341: 4)
- History of the Atlantic Movement, 1986-1994 (Box-folder 341: 5-6)
  Includes four microcassettes, "Tapes of S. Stone, R. Bowie, R. Pfaltzgraff."
- Societal Problem areas, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 341: 7)
- Biographies, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 341: 8)
- Speeches of Huntley, 2000 (Box-folder 341: 9)
- Huntley biographies, 2000-2007 (Box-folder 341: 10)
  Includes photograph of Huntley.
- Pax Democratica, 2003-2008 (Box-folder 342: 1)
- Committees for a Community of Democracies
  - General, 2004-2009 (Box-folder 342: 2-3)
  - Board, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 342: 4)
- Program and substance, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 342: 5)
- Restructuring and correspondence, 2007 (Box-folder 342: 6)
- Obama, United State government, 2009 March-September (Box-folder 342: 7)
- Cabinet, 2006-2008 (Box-folder 343: 1)
- Grawemeyer Award, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 343: 2)
- Jackson School of International Studies (JSIS), International Security Conference, 2007 January (Box-folder 343: 3)
- Spady Forum Foundation, 2007 March-July (Box-folder 343: 4)
- Wheel and circle charts (Box-folder 343: 5)
  Includes transparencies.
- Snake charts, 2007 January (Box-folder 343: 6)
- General ideas and data (Box-folder 343: 7)
- Other graphics (Box-folder 343: 8)
- Letters to public officials, 1975-2009 (Box-folder 343: 9-11)
- Correspondence
  - 1996-1999 (Box-folder 344: 1)
  - 2004-2005 (Box-folder 344: 2)
  - 2005-2006 (Box-folder 344: 3-4)
  - 2009 (Box-folder 344: 5)
- Bruce Bishop, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 344: 6)
- Gen. Wesley K. Clark, 2003 (Box-folder 344: 7)
- R. Foulon, 1998 (Box-folder 345: 1)
- A. Hoffman, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 345: 2)
- David Barton, 1988-2004 (Box-folder 345: 3-5)
- John M. Davis, 1989-2006 (Box-folder 345: 6-7)
- R. Gastil, 1992-2004 (Box-folder 345: 8-9)
- John Ikenberry, 1994-2006 (Box-folder 346: 1-2)
- Chris Jones, 1995-2006 (Box-folder 346: 3)
- Marilou Smith Goldstein, 1990-2004 (Box-folder 346: 4)
- Arthur Hoffman, 2000-2004 (Box-folder 346: 5-6)
- Rick Meade, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 346: 7)
- Terry Moyemont, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 346: 8)
- Ancil Payne, 2001-2004 (Box-folder 346: 9)
- Eagleburger, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 346: 10)
- Dale Turner, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 347: 1)
- G. Modelski, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 347: 2)
- John and Freida Parker, 1990-1997 (Box-folder 347: 3)
- W. Raymond, 1992 (Box-folder 347: 4)
- Sutton, Francis X., 2002-2003 (Box-folder 347: 5)
- Jesse Swingle, 2001-2006 (Box-folder 347: 6-7)
- Don Vollmer, 1998-2006 (Box-folder 347: 8)
- Lars Uhrdin, 1994-1998 (Box-folder 347: 9)
- Tiziana Stella, 1994-2004 (Box-folder 347: 10-12)
- Correspondence with publishers and editors, 1980-1995 (Box-folder 348: 1-2)
- Pax Democratica
  - Publishers, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 348: 3)
  - Proposals and turn downs, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 348: 4)
  - U.S. proposals and turndowns, 1996 (Box-folder 348: 5)
  - Macmillan, general, 1998-2002 (Box-folder 348: 6)
  - Proposals and negotiations, 1997 (Box-folder 348: 7)
  - Publishing and editing, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 348: 8-9)
  - Macmillan marketing, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 348: 10-13)
  - Paperback edition, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 349: 1)
  - Foreign editions, 1996, 2000 (Box-folder 349: 2)
  - St. Martin's Press, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 349: 3-4)
  - Consultant R. Rowson, 1996-1998, 2000 (Box-folder 349: 5)
  - St. Martin's Press, Huntley's orders, 2000, 2003 (Box-folder 349: 6)
  - Promotion by Next Century Initiative and Committees for a Community of Democracies, 1996-2002 (Box-folder 349: 7)
  - Promotions, 1997-2004 (Box-folder 349: 8)
  - Personal gifts, 1998-2003 (Box-folder 349: 9)
  - Reviews and reactions, 1995-2002 (Box-folder 349: 10)
  - Future editions, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 349: 11)
- Russian "Marshall Plan of Idea?,", 1989-1994 (Box-folder 350: 1)
- Atlantic-Pacific Debate ("Goodbye Europe?"), 1988 (Box-folder 350: 2)
- Publishing, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 350: 3)
- Projects
  - Leadership (Box-folder 350: 4)
  - A/P bibliography, 1976 (Box-folder 350: 5)
  - "Power, Love, and Law,", 1975 (Box-folder 350: 6)
- Memoirs, III, 1976-1985 (Box-folder 350: 7-8)
  Includes stamps.
- Memoirs, IV, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 350: 9-10)
- "The Great Novel!,", 1990 May-June (Box-folder 350: 11)
- Mac Macdonald, 1988-2007 (Box-folder 351: 1)
- Sir Michael Palliser, 2000-2006 (Box-folder 351: 2)
- C. Patrick, 1995-2006 (Box-folder 351: 3)
- Gail Stewart, Pax Democratica, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 351: 4)
- Jesse Swingle, 2007- (Box-folder 351: 5)
- Carl Jensen, 2006 November (Box-folder 351: 6)
- Jim Lobe, 2004 November (Box-folder 351: 7)
- Dean Mahin, 2002-2005 (Box-folder 351: 8)
- Dick Robinson 06, 2006 August-November (Box-folder 351: 9)
- R. J. Rummel, 1996, 2001 (Box-folder 352: 1)
- Valerie Aubourg, 2000-2007 (Box-folder 352: 2)
- Jim Braden, 2004-2007 (Box-folder 352: 3)
- Robert Brand, 1990-2007 (Box-folder 352: 4)
- A. Hoffman, 2007-, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 352: 5)
- Adrienne Janus, 1990-2007 (Box-folder 352: 6)
- D. Kilgour, 2002-2007 (Box-folder 352: 7)
- Memoirs
  - General, 2002-2005 (Box-folder 353: 1)
  - Early draft pages, 2005 August (Box-folder 353: 2)
  - Manuscript materials, 3rd edition, 2004 (Box-folder 353: 3)
  - Publishing, 2004-2006 (Box-folder 353: 4)
  - Publishers, New Academia, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 353: 5)
  - Ploys to publishers, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 353: 6)
  - Publishers and contracts, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 353: 7)
  - Correspondence with publishers and editors, 1996-2007 (Box-folder 353: 8-9)
  - Publishing details and plans, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 353: 10)
    Includes compact disc.
  - Publishing funds, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 353: 11)
  - A.U. Seminar, 2005 August-September (Box-folder 353: 12)
  - DC book launch, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 354: 1)
  - Seattle book launch, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 354: 2)
  - Orders, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 354: 3)
  - Book reviews, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 354: 4)
  - Cover, jacket, 2005 (Box-folder 354: 5)
  - Sales, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 354: 6)
  - Mailing lists, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 354: 7)
  - Copyright, 2006 November (Box-folder 354: 8)
  - Distribution, publicity, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 354: 9)
  - Gifts, personal, 2006 (Box-folder 355: 1)
  - Gifts, CCD and others, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 355: 2)
  - Text, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 355: 3-4)
  - Cuts and illustrations, 2004-2006 (Box-folder 355: 5)
  - Preliminary materials, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 355: 6)
  - Pen sketches, 2005 August (Box-folder 355: 7)
  - Appendices, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 355: 8)
  - Index, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 355: 9)
  - Preliminary, forward, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 355: 10)
  - Book materials, 2005 (Box-folder 355: 11)
    Includes 2 compact discs.
- Committees for a Community of Democracies
  - General, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 356: 1-4)
  - Fundraising, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 356: 5)
  - Russell, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 356: 6)
  - Borden, 2004-2008 (Box-folder 357: 1-2)
  - Gates, 2006-2008 (Box-folder 357: 3)
  - Associates, 2007 May-August (Box-folder 357: 4)
  - International, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 357: 5-6)
  - UK Mortier, 2003-2007 (Box-folder 358: 1-4)
  - J. Rogers, 2003-2007 (Box-folder 358: 5-6)
  - Substance program, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 359: 1-2)
  - Princeton Report, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 359: 3)
  - Foreign policy, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 359: 4)
  - Program on tertiary education, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 359: 5)
  - Policy issues, 2001-2006 (Box-folder 360: 1-2)
  - Foreign policy, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 360: 3)
- Publications, 2002 July (Box-folder 360: 4)
- Hoover Institution, 1982, 2003-2007 (Box-folder 360: 5)
- State museum, 2007 May (Box-folder 360: 6)
- International relations, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 361: 1-2)
- Far Right, Far Left, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 361: 3)
- Democracy and civic culture, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 361: 4)
- UN and affiliates, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 361: 5)
- World economy, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 361: 6)
- Atlantic, security, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 361: 7)
- NATO, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 361: 8)
- Atlantic Movement, young historians, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 362: 1)
- Europe development, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 362: 2)
- Individual countries and regions, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 362: 3)
- International education, 1953, 2002 (Box-folder 362: 4)
- Non-governmental organizations (NGOs), 2005-2007 (Box-folder 362: 5)
- Federal Union, Association to Unite the Democracies (AUD), and successors, 1975, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 362: 6)
- Philanthropy, 2007 (Box-folder 362: 7)
- Societal problems, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 362: 8)
- Seoul
  - Plans, NGOs, 2002 (Box-folder 363: 1)
  - Arrangements, NGOs, 2002 (Box-folder 363: 2)
  - Results and communiques, NGOs, 2002 (Box-folder 363: 3)
  - Press and media, NGOs, 2002 (Box-folder 363: 4)
  - Participants, NGOs, 2002 (Box-folder 363: 5)
  - Preliminaries, Community of Democracies, 2002 (Box-folder 363: 6)
  - Results, Community of Democracies, 2002 (Box-folder 363: 7)
  - Press and media, Community of Democracies, 2002 (Box-folder 363: 8)
  - NGO forum results, 2002 (Box-folder 363: 9)
- Santiago
  - Substance, Community of Democracies, 2004 (Box-folder 363: 10)
  - Plans and accomplishments, Community of Democracies, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 363: 11)
  - Arrangements, Community of Democracies, 2004 May (Box-folder 363: 12)
  - Participants, Community of Democracies, 2005 (Box-folder 363: 13)
  - Press and media, Community of Democracies, 2005 (Box-folder 363: 14)
  - Plans, NGO, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 363: 15)
  - Democracy education, 2003 (Box-folder 363: 16)
  - Democracy review, NGO, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 363: 17)
- Bamako, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 363: 18)
- Committees for a Community of Democracies
  - Table of contents, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 364: 1)
  - Associates, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 364: 2)
  - Rosters of members and biographies, 2001 (Box-folder 364: 3)
  - Program, 2003 (Box-folder 364: 4)
  - Mission and strategy, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 364: 5)
  - Finance budgets, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 364: 6)
  - International initiatives, 2003 (Box-folder 364: 7)
  - Institute of World Community Studies, 1994-2003 (Box-folder 364: 8)
  - Substance, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 364: 9)
  - International correspondents, 2003 (Box-folder 364: 10)
  - Legal documents, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 364: 11)
  - Board meetings, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 364: 12)
  - Transition and government, 2000-2003 (Box-folder 364: 13)
  - Table of contents, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 364: 14)
  - Mission and strategy, 2005 (Box-folder 364: 15)
  - Rosters of members and biographies, 2004 (Box-folder 364: 16)
  - Program, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 364: 17)
  - Finance and budgets, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 364: 18)
  - International initiatives, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 364: 19)
  - Substance, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 364: 20)
  - International correspondents, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 364: 21)
  - Board meetings, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 364: 22)
  - Transition and government, 2005 September (Box-folder 364: 23)
  - Mission and strategy, 2006 (Box-folder 365: 1)
  - Rosters of members and biographies, 2006 (Box-folder 365: 2)
  - Program, 2006 (Box-folder 365: 3)
  - Finance and budgets, 2006 (Box-folder 365: 4)
  - International initiatives (Box-folder 365: 5)
  - Substance, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 365: 6)
  - Board meetings, 2006 (Box-folder 365: 7)
  - Associates, 2007 (Box-folder 365: 8)
  - Mission and strategy, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 365: 9)
  - Rosters of members and biographies, 2006-2008 (Box-folder 365: 10)
  - Program, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 365: 11)
  - Finance and budgets, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 365: 12)
  - International initiatives, 2008 (Box-folder 365: 13)
  - Substance, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 365: 14)
  - Board meetings, 2006-2008 (Box-folder 365: 15)
  - Mission and strategy, 2009 February (Box-folder 365: 16)
  - Rosters of members and biographies, 2009 (Box-folder 365: 17)
  - Program, 2009 (Box-folder 365: 18)
  - Substance, 2009 (Box-folder 365: 19)
  - Board meetings, 2009 (Box-folder 365: 20)
- Distribution list
  - BASICS Country Reports, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 366: 1)
  - "Committees for a Community of Democracies" pamphlet, draft, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 366: 2)
  - Monitor and annual review, 1981 (Box-folder 366: 3)
  - "France Under Mitterrand,", 1981 August (Box-folder 366: 4)
  - Principles and program, undated (Box-folder 366: 5)
  - Council of Democracies, undated (Box-folder 366: 6)
  - Consortium for Atlantic-Pacific Affairs (CAPA) Ivory Prospectus, undated (Box-folder 366: 7)
  - Atlantic Institute, early days and personal notes, undated (Box-folder 366: 8)
  - "Japan in International Society of Future,", 1981 March (Box-folder 366: 9)
  - "Mini-NATO in Pacific?,", 1981 March (Box-folder 366: 10)
  - Task force statement, 1981 March (Box-folder 366: 11)
  - Bridging Conference, undated (Box-folder 366: 12)
  - International Community of the Democracies, undated (Box-folder 366: 13)
  - Tan CAPA Prospectus, 1981 June (Box-folder 366: 14)
  - COC, statement of purpose, undated (Box-folder 366: 15)
    Possibly Committees of Correspondence.
  - COC paper, 1980 September (Box-folder 366: 16)
  - Committees for a Community of Democracies people lists, undated (Box-folder 366: 17)
  - Preliminary concepts, undated (Box-folder 366: 18)
  - "Challenge of International Community,", undated (Box-folder 366: 19)
  - Table, Huntley effort analysis, undated (Box-folder 366: 20)
  - "Successor Generation," Atlantic Institute paper, 1981 April (Box-folder 366: 21)
  - Uniting the Democracies, 1981 October (Box-folder 366: 22)
  - Uniting the Democracies, flyer, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 366: 23)
  - Battelle human resource data, 1980 March (Box-folder 366: 24)
  - BASICS summary, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 366: 25)
  - Die Welt article, undated (Box-folder 366: 26)
  - Consortium for Atlantic-Pacific Affairs (CAPA) review, 1979 August (Box-folder 366: 27)
  - "Aiding the Underdeveloped,", undated (Box-folder 366: 28)
  - BASICS Strategic Cont. Forecasting Future, 1980 October (Box-folder 366: 29)
  - BASICS proposal, 1980 May (Box-folder 366: 30)
  - "Japanese-Western Relations,", undated (Box-folder 366: 31)
  - NATO review article, undated (Box-folder 366: 32)
  - Short Prospectus C, undated (Box-folder 366: 33)
  - Prospectus C, 1978 September (Box-folder 366: 34)
  - Consortium for Atlantic-Pacific Affairs (CAPA) International Adv. Board, 1978 (Box-folder 366: 35)
  - Consortium for Atlantic-Pacific Affairs (CAPA) board of directors, undated (Box-folder 366: 36)
  - Historic origins, undated (Box-folder 366: 37)
  - Wheel chart, undated (Box-folder 366: 38)
  - Global significance, undated (Box-folder 366: 39)
  - Historic or modern, undated (Box-folder 366: 40)
  - "Western World/Will to Survive,", 1978 December (Box-folder 366: 41)
  - Consortium for Atlantic-Pacific Affairs (CAPA) Prospectus A, concept paper, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 366: 42)
  - Prospectus B, 1978 May (Box-folder 366: 43)
  - "Extending the Atlantic System,", undated (Box-folder 366: 44)
  - Core program, undated (Box-folder 366: 45)
  - NIRA paper, undated (Box-folder 366: 46)
  - Lecture given at U.W., 1976 November (Box-folder 366: 47)
  - National cultural profiles, undated (Box-folder 366: 48)
  - "Interim Report,", undated (Box-folder 366: 49)
  - Summary, June Consortium for Atlantic-Pacific Affairs (CAPA) meeting, 1977 June (Box-folder 366: 50)
  - Huntley-Odegaard draft, undated (Box-folder 366: 51)